(Amy:)Sheldon, please stop
trying to seduce me.
(Sheldon:)Who's trying to seduce you?
(Sheldon:)After a long day I always
turn on smooth jazz
(Sheldon:)and spray deer musk
on my inner thighs.
(Amy:)I thought it smelled
like a petting zoo in here.
(Sheldon:)Anything you'd like to pet?
(Sheldon:)Not my hair. There's
a lot of goop in it.
(Amy:)Okay, I've had enough.
(Sheldon:)Amy, come back.
(Raj:)I don't know
how to open the oysters.
(Raj:)So, um, what
surprised you the most
(Raj:)when you first
came to America?
(Isabella:)Well, I suppose
how much people care
about Oprah's favorite things.
(Raj:)I thought that, too.
(Raj:)But then I got
my first waffle maker
(Raj:)and never questioned her again.
(Sheldon:)You know,
(Isabella:)I do have some time off
this Sunday
(Isabella:)- if you'd like to...
- Hey! I saw your car...
(Howard:)Oh, sorry.
Am I interrupting?
(Cleaner:)Uh...
(Raj:)It's okay.
Uh, I should get back to work.